https://www.aveno.be/p/privacy-cookies.html

Register on our site
To be able to use Aveno digital services, we request users to register by filling in certain details online. The data that the user fills in the boxes relating to name, company, possibly address, e-mail address, and telephone, we call the "registration data".
Contact details
If you, after reading our privacy statement, have questions about this or wish to contact us, please contact us via the following contact details:Adres: Nieuwelandenweg 32 /1, 2030 AntwerpenTelephone: +32 3 544 18 17E-mail: aveno@aveno.beWebsite: http://aveno.be/Ondernemingsnr: BE 0864.281.282
Why do we process personal data
Your personal data are processed by Aveno for the following purposes and legal grounds:
To participate in the activities of Aveno; (execution agreement)
Sending newsletters and invitations. (permission of the person concerned)
We use the collected data only for the purposes for which we obtained the data.
Provision to third parties
We may provide the information you give to us to third parties if this is necessary for the execution of the above described purposes.
For example, we use a third party for:
Taking care of newsletters and invitations.
We never pass on personal data to other parties with whom we have not entered into a processor agreement. With these parties, we of course make the necessary arrangements for security your personal data.Furthermore, we will not pass on the information you provide to third parties, unless this is legally required and permitted. An example of this is that the police request us in the context of an investigation data.
In such a case, we must cooperate and are therefore obliged to provide this information. We do not provide personal data to parties which are located outside the EU.
Storage period
Aveno stores personal data for a maximum of 5 years after the last use for the purpose for which they were provided or required by law.
Security of the data
We have taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data against unlawful processing, for example we have taken the following measures;All persons who are able to access your data on behalf of Aveno are obliged to maintain their confidentiality.We use a username and password policy on all our systems;
Your rights regarding your data
You have the right to inspect and right to correct or remove the personal data we have received from you. At the top of this privacy statement is how you can contact us. You can also contact us via the contact page of our website.You can also object to the processing of your personal data by us or by one of our processors.You also have the right to have the data provided by you transferred by us to yourself or by order of you directly to another party. We can ask you to identify you before we can comply with the aforementioned requests.Use of cookiesDuring a visit to our website 'cookies' can be placed on the hard disk of your computer. A cookie is a text file that is placed by the server of a website in the browser of your computer or on your mobile device when you consult a website. Cookies can not be used to identify people, a cookie can only identify a machine.You can set your internet browser in such a way that cookies are not accepted, that you receive a warning when a cookie is installed or that the cookies are subsequently removed from your hard drive. You can do this via the settings of your browser (via the help function). Keep in mind that certain graphic elements can not appear correctly, or that you will not be able to use certain applications.By using our website, you agree to our use of cookies.
Complaints
If you have a complaint about the processing of your personal data, we ask you to contact us directly.You always have the right to file a complaint with the Privacy Commission, this is the supervisory authority in the field of privacy protection.
[STAFF PICK]_$type=sticky$show=/p/contact.html$c=4$m=0$l=1$icon=1$h=318
staff pick
$show=/p/faq.html$type=list$m=0$c=20$p=1
faq
$show=/p/faq.html
[STAFF PICK]_$type=sticky$show=/p/faq.html$c=4$m=0$l=1$icon=1$h=318
staff pick
$show=/p/jobs.html$type=three$c=3$au=0$cm=0$p=1
jobs
$show=/p/sustainability.html$type=blogging$l=1$c=5$m=0$p=1
sustainability
[STAFF PICK]_$type=sticky$show=/p/sustainability.html$c=4$m=0$l=1$icon=1$h=318
staff pick
$show=/p/quality.html$type=two$h=240$m=0$l=0$sn=0$rm=0$c=6$p=1
quality
$show=/p/products.html$type=three$h=240$m=0$l=0$sn=0$rm=0$c=6$p=1
products
$show=/p/news.html$type=one$au=0$cm=0$rm=1$sn=1$c=5$p=1
news
[STAFF PICK]_$type=sticky$show=/p/news.html$c=4$m=0$l=1$icon=1$h=318
staff pick
[ABOUT US]_$show=/p/about.html$type=blogging$l=1$c=3$m=0
about
[STAFF PICK]_$type=sticky$show=/p/about.html$c=4$m=0$l=1$icon=1$h=318
staff pick
[JOBS]_$type=slider$sn=0$l=1$c=6$m=0$show=home
jobs
/fa-share-alt/ SHARE & TRANSLATE
/fa-envelope-o/ SUBSCRIBE NEWSLETTER
E-mail address
View previous campaigns.
/fa-clock-o/ MOST RECENT UPDATES$type=blogging$m=0$l=0$sn=0$rm=0$c=7$va=0$show=post
about
bi-weekly
exhibition
faq
in de kijker
industry
jobs
monthly
/fa-fire/ TRENDING THIS MONTH$type=one$hide=post
What is the difference between Canola and Rapeseed Oil?
Have you ever wondered whether Canola is the same as Rapeseed Oil? In Belgium, the answer is yes. Rapeseed oil is the name given to ...
Magazijnier (M/V)
Functiebeschrijving
Als magazijnier ben je verantwoordelijk voor de ontvangst, opslag, groeperen/order picken van in- en uitgaande goe...
Machine operator (M/V)
Functiebeschrijving
Als machine operator ben je verantwoordelijk voor het bedienen en controleren van afvullijnen en verpakkingsmachines...
© 2015
Aveno NV - The one stop shop for all your Oils and Fats
All rights reserved.
Home
About
Products
Quality
FAQ
Webmaster
Privacy & Cookies
Contact
Message
about,3,bi-weekly,33,exhibition,2,faq,21,in de kijker,2,industry,6,jobs,3,monthly,11,news,41,newsletter,44,nieuws,5,products,5,quality,5,staff pick,13,sustainability,9,
ltr
static_page
Aveno NV - The one stop shop for all your Oils and Fats: Privacy & Cookies
Can not copy the codes / texts, please press [CTRL]+[C] (or CMD+C with Mac) to copy
Type something and Enter
Search
